[{"answer": " Hey Matt.  Whats up", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hey, man.  Nothing much.  Im just trying to figure out where to go next year.  It", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hey Matt.  Whats up", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yeah, tell me about it.  My parents want me to go to a university thats close t", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Hey, man.  Nothing much.  Im just trying to figure out where to go next year.  It", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Mine too.  Where are you thinking of going?  Im thinking about several loca", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Yeah, tell me about it.  My parents want me to go to a university thats close t", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " How so", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Mine too.  Where are you thinking of going?  Im thinking about several loca", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Well, Georgia State is a lot smaller and its an urban school, so it doesnt reall", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " How so", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Having a nice campus sounds cool", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well, Georgia State is a lot smaller and its an urban school, so it doesnt reall", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Yeah, it really does.  Plus, UGA has a really big greek life, which would be s", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Having a nice campus sounds cool", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": "Man, think of all the parties", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Yeah, it really does.  Plus, UGA has a really big greek life, which would be s", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " I know, I know.  That part would be great.  The only bad thing is that I wa", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Man, think of all the parties", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Does Georgia State have one", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 44, "question": " I know, I know.  That part would be great.  The only bad thing is that I wa", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Yeah, they have a pretty big and well-known Urban Planning Department.  So, i", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Does Georgia State have one", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " What do you think is more important  academics or the campus life", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Yeah, they have a pretty big and well-known Urban Planning Department.  So, i", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Well, I know I should say academics, but having fun at college is really mor", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " What do you think is more important  academics or the campus life", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Me too.  Haha!  Thats why Im trying to get accepted to Duke.  Its a major part", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Well, I know I should say academics, but having fun at college is really mor", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Ive heard about that one.  What about The University of California?  Do you kno", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Me too.  Haha!  Thats why Im trying to get accepted to Duke.  Its a major part", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Not a lot.  I think its close to the ocean and its a pretty cool place to live i", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Ive heard about that one.  What about The University of California?  Do you kno", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I could surf every weekend if I went there.  Id love to go to California, but m", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Not a lot.  I think its close to the ocean and its a pretty cool place to live i", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Whoa, how would you do that?  Thats like $100,000", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 71, "question": " I could surf every weekend if I went there.  Id love to go to California, but m", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " I guess I would take out a student loan or get a scholarship or something", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Whoa, how would you do that?  Thats like $100,000", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " You?  A scholarship?  I dont think so", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 73, "question": " I guess I would take out a student loan or get a scholarship or something", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Shut up, man.  I have pretty good grades, maybe I could get one", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " You?  A scholarship?  I dont think so", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Id start thinking about going to a local university if I were you", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Shut up, man.  I have pretty good grades, maybe I could get one", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " It would definitely be easier", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Id start thinking about going to a local university if I were you", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Well, have you applied to UGA and Georgia State yet", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 77, "question": " It would definitely be easier", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Not yet.  Im still writing my application essays.  The deadline is May 1, so I stil", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Well, have you applied to UGA and Georgia State yet", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I sent mine last week", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Not yet.  Im still writing my application essays.  The deadline is May 1, so I stil", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Youre applying there too?  Awesome!  If we both get in, we should roo", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 86, "question": " I sent mine last week", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Ok, lets do it", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Youre applying there too?  Awesome!  If we both get in, we should roo", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Cool.    I heard the dorms at UGA are really nice", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Ok, lets do it", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Yeah, I heard the same thing", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Cool.    I heard the dorms at UGA are really nice", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " I guess I should go work on my applications.  If I dont submit them in time,  ", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Yeah, I heard the same thing", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Youd better work on those.  Call me later.  Maybe we can hang out thi", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 97, "question": " I guess I should go work on my applications.  If I dont submit them in time,  ", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Ok, Ill call you", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Youd better work on those.  Call me later.  Maybe we can hang out thi", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Later", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Ok, Ill call you", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": "Later", "docId": "04-08", "aSentId": 103, "question": " Later", "qSentId": 102}]
